All right, so let's build a game. For
this specific game, we're not going to
let AI just make up the idea for the
game. My producer Dave and I have been
actually brainstorming an idea for a
game that we thought would be fun to
make. The game is tentatively called
Library Survivors, very similar to the
Vampire Survivors game, but you're
playing as a librarian. You need to put
away books while rowdy kids take more
books off the shelves and then leave
them scattered all over the map. As the
librarian, you go around and you pick up
the books and you put them back on the
bookshelf. As the game goes on, more and
more kids enter the library. They become
more rambunctious. They pull more books
off the bookshelf. And your job is to
continually pick up these books and put
them back on the bookshelf before you
get overwhelmed. There's a little chaos
meter. And with this chaos meter, the
more books are on the ground, the faster
the chaos meter goes up. And you got to
get all the books up off the ground
before the chaos meter hits 100%. Sounds
a little complicated if you know Vampire
Survivors. It's sort of like this
reverse vampire survivors game where you
have swarms and swarms of kids, but the
kids are actually trying to avoid the
librarian while causing chaos while the
librarian is sort of trying to chase the
kids around and pick up books and put
them back on the shelf. So, now that
we've got the concept for the game, I
went ahead and typed out the basic idea
of the game, but I want ChatGpt to help
flesh it out more. Please help me flesh
out the following game concept. help me
with the gameplay loop, the power-ups,
the win and lose scenarios, how to
increase difficulty over time, and any
other gameplay elements that are
necessary that I'm not fully thinking
through. Now, for this, I'm actually
going to upgrade it to 03 Pro, but if
you only have 03 or 40, it'll still do a
pretty good job. I just want it to spend
a little bit more time thinking through
this one. And we'll go ahead and submit
it. And it probably will take a minute
or so for it to really reason through
and think about this game. So, it took
GPT a little over 5 minutes to think
about this, and it put together a fairly
extensive outline and breakdown of what
this game should be. It included
everything from gameplay mechanics to
character upgrades to sound effects and
graphic recommendations. All in all, a
really solid first effort from ChatGpt.
Here are two screenshots that you can
pause in case you want to read the
entire conversation. So, we've got a
pretty well fleshed out concept. There's
a few other things that I think are
missing from this brief that I'm going
to add in real quick. So things like
kids shouldn't just knock books off the
shelves. They should also be able to
take the books and run away and drop
them in other places of the library to
create more chaos. The player should be
able to see when a kid is carrying a
book so that the player can actually
chase the kid down and take the book
away from them. Kids should actually
actively try to run away from the
librarian. Over time, more and more
books should be available to come off
the shelves so that the difficulty
increases with the volume of books as
well. And with each level the player is
at, it should get more and more
difficult to level up. So going from a
level one to a level two should require
10 XP, but going from a level two to a
level three should require 20. And it
should get harder and harder to level up
each time. And I'm going to say, please
update the brief with this additional
info and create a markdown file with a
full explanation and all of the gameplay
details that we've decided upon. All
right. So now it's going to add that
stuff to the brief, but give me a
markdown file that we can use and pull
into our next step. All right. And after
about 4 and 1/2 minutes, it says, "I
folded your five new mechanics into the
kit AI difficulty curve and player
interaction system, then compiled
everything into a single markdown brief.
Here's our markdown brief. We'll
download it. And we've got a pretty
decent breakdown. Now it's time to move
on to the coding phase. And to do the
coding, I'm going to use Claude Code.
Now, I haven't played with Claude Code a
ton. I did a tweet recently asking what
your favorite tools are, what I should
spend more time messing with, and
probably overwhelmingly the one that
people said the most was spend more time
with Claude Code. It's really good. So,
I've spent the last couple days sort of
learning the basics of Claude Code, and
yeah, I really like it. So, we're going
to build out this game using Claude
Code. I don't want to go too deep into a
tutorial, but here's the quick rundown
of how to get Claude Code working on
your computer. So, if you head on over
to enthropic.com/claude-code,
this is where you're going to be able to
get the instructions. The first thing
you need to do, install NodeJS on your
computer. Simply click on this link,
download it for your operating system,
run the installer. Once that's
installed, it wants you to run this
command here inside of your terminal.
Now, personally, I still like to use an
IDE when I'm using Claude Code. An IDE
would be like Visual Studio Code or
Cursor or Windsurf or something like
that. And you can install claude code
inside the terminal inside of one of
those apps. It's really simple to do.
I'm actually going to use Windsurf, but
let me show you using VS Code. If you
head to code.visisualstudio.com,
download it for your operating system.
Once you have VS Code set up on your
desktop, come over to this little button
here that says extensions. It's got like
three little squares and a diamond. And
then up under search, search out Claude.
And you'll see Claude Code for VS Code
here. Now, if you're in Windsurf or
Cursor, it will look identical. Windsurf
and Cursor are forks of VS Code, you
would install the exact same extension
and do it the exact same way. So, we'll
go ahead and click install to install
this extension. We'll trust the
publisher and install. And now you can
see we've got Claude Code installed.
Now, when you're inside a tool like VS
Code or Windsurf, you want to have a
folder open where it's going to save all
of your files. So, we'll go ahead and
click on this little explorer icon in
the top left. Click open folder. I have
a folder on my computer that I just call
code. and I'll create a new folder
inside of code called library survivors.
We'll click create and then we'll open
this folder as our folder in the
explorer here. And now we're good to
start creating. You can see that when I
installed that extension, it put the
little Claude logo up in the top right
of my VS Code. So, if I click on this
link here, it's going to fire up Claude
Code for me. Now, the first time you use
it, it's going to have some setup
instructions. Go ahead and click yes to
proceed. And you can literally start
using Claude Code by typing right here.
Now again, I use Windsurf over VS Code.
So I'm actually going to close out of VS
Code and we'll just pick up where we
left off in Windsurf. You can see it
looks the same. Same icons on the left
side. If I click on plugins here, you
can see I've got the Claude Code plugin
installed. It works exactly the same
way. We'll go ahead and open our folder.
Go into code, open library survivors,
and I'm going to build basically the
same exact way just inside of Windsurf.
I'm going to go ahead and rightclick,
click new text file. And when I do this,
you can see we got our run Cloud Code
button up here. So, I'm just going to go
ahead and click that. And it's going to
open up Cloud Code in our little
terminal. I'm actually going to close
out of this. And over in our explorer
here, I'm actually going to take that
brief that we created earlier, and I'm
just going to toss it over into our new
folder. So, now it's got the brief of
what we want to create. We can actually
preview the whole brief that ChatGpt
wrote up about this game. And one thing
that's really cool about using Claude
code is down here I can click shift tab
and you can see that I can turn on auto
accept edits. So as it writes code I can
tell it just go ahead and update
everything and just auto create it. If I
hit shift tab again it puts on plan mode
where it maps out a plan for creating
whatever it is you're going to build.
But it won't actually write code yet.
And I really like to use this plan mode
to figure out what the next steps are.
have it map out a plan and then move on
to the next step of coding up the plan
that it just came up with. That way if
part of the plan doesn't make sense, you
can tell it to, you know, reconfigure
the plan a little bit and then move on.
All right, so to start planning, what
I'm going to do is I'm going to come up
to this library survivor design MD,
rightclick. I'm going to copy the path
here and then in my prompt box, I'm
going to say map out a plan to develop
the game in this brief. And then I'm
going to go ahead and paste in the path
that we just copied. I'm going to hit
enter and it's going to just start doing
its thing. And just like that, Cloud
Code got started. It put together an
extremely welldetailed development
roadmap for us. And it included things
like the game engine and even the
expected development times, which kind
of made me laugh because I'm doing all
of this in just a day. But for the first
version, I wanted to do something a bit
quicker and simpler than what it
suggested. So I asked it to revise the
road map and develop the game in
JavaScript, which it did perfectly. So
now the last step was to have it create
a new markdown file with this road map
so we can refer back to it later. Now
comes the coolest part about claude
code. I can just tell it go build the
thing now and just walk away from my
computer. It might take 10 minutes or
so, but it'll just start building it. So
I'm going to go ahead and leave it on
auto accept edits here. We'll grab our
development plan, copy the path, follow
the plan mapped out here, and build the
game that we designed here. And then
I'll grab this path. And there's
probably a better way to do this. I'm
sure I'm going to get all sorts of
comments that are like, "Oh, you're
doing this way too slow. You can do it
by clicking this hotkey or that thing or
whatever." I'm so new to coding and
you're learning that right now. If
you're a pro coder and you're watching
this video, you're probably going to see
me make a lot of mistakes. But if you're
not a procoder and you want to make your
own game, you're seeing everything I do,
mistakes and all. So, let's go ahead and
have it build this out following the
plan and the design. We'll leave auto
accept edits on and just hit enter. and
it's just going to do its thing. I'll
start building library survivors
following the development plan. Let me
begin with phase one core foundation.
It's building a checklist now of
everything it needs to do. And you can
see it's just going to go now. And at
this point, it's asking me if I want to
proceed cuz it needs to run some extra
initialization stuff. Let's just go
ahead and say yes and don't ask again.
So, it just goes and does the stuff it's
supposed to do. We'll see over here it's
starting to actually build out new files
and the game is now underway. So cool. I
could just kind of step away and let it
do its thing now.
[Music]
So now it gave us a summary here and we
can see everything that it did. I've
successfully built the foundation of
library survivors following the
development plan, project setup, game
loop, state management, input system,
asset loading, camera system, rendering
system, player energy, etc., etc. Now,
it says run npm rundev to play the game
at localhost 3000. So, let's go ahead
and do that. I'm going to go ahead and
open up a terminal. I do this by
clicking up in the top right this little
I don't know how to describe this
button, but it's got like a larger box
on top and a smaller rectangle on the
bottom. I click this. This opens up my
terminal down here directly inside of
wind surf. I can copy this npm rundev
here. Paste it down into this terminal.
And we get a screen that looks like
this. Library survivors. It's got start
game instructions and settings. Says you
can use the arrow keys or WS to
navigate. Those don't appear to be
working. Yeah, it's pretty much just a
frozen screen here. So, let's jump back
to Wind Surf here. First, switch it to
plan mode. I tried opening the game on
local host and the menu loads up, but
nothing works. Arrow keys, WS buttons,
mouse clicks, etc. None of it is working
when attempting to play the game. We'll
go ahead and submit that and let it
review its code. See if we can find the
problem. Okay, it seems like it found
the issue after about a minute of
thinking. It figured out the error,
explain the changes needed, and says
it's a simple fix. So, let's go ahead
and just click yes and accept edits. And
a few minutes later, it says try
refreshing the browser, and the controls
should work. Now, let's go check this
out here. Refresh. Uh, still no luck
here. So, I'm still running into some
issues after some back and forth. This
time, it told me to check the console
and send over any issues it's seeing in
the console. I tried again. And as you
can see, I'm clicking buttons, but
nothing is working over in the main
screen. But as I click down or one of
these arrow keys, you can see in the
console, it is noticing that I'm
clicking these buttons. Just nothing's
happening on the homepage. So, I'm going
to go ahead and in this console here,
rightclick, copy console, jump back to
Windsurf, and I'll say it's still not
working. Here is the contents of the
console. And then I'll just kind of give
it a space, and then paste everything in
here and hit enter. Here's everything
that it saw in the console. So, it can
actually read that and figure out the
issue. And I'm going to continue my
troubleshooting now. All right. After
several back and forth messages with
Claude Code saying, "Hey, it still
didn't work. Try again. Still didn't
work. Try again." I finally got
something that seemingly works. So, I
can actually press up and down or SNW or
the mouse doesn't work yet, but the
keyboard works with it. Settings doesn't
do anything. If I click on settings,
nothing happens. Instructions gives us
some basic instructions here. Hitting
escape comes back to the main menu. And
if I click start game, you can see we're
in the game. However, that chaos meter
at the top is going insanely fast and
we're already a game over. So, it's not
quite working the way we want it to. The
game loop isn't quite doing what we
want. It's time to get into actually
refining and dialing in the game. But
before we do that, I want to tell you
about this really cool platform that
I've been playing with. And this is not
sponsored. This is just something that I
thought was cool and wanted to share
with you. And it's called Deli. If you
head on over to deli.ai/mattwolf,
this is trained on my YouTube videos, my
podcast, my newsletter, various blog
posts I've written, things like that.
And you can actually ask it questions
and it will respond in a way that I
would likely respond because it's
trained on all of this information I've
put onto the web. So, I can ask it a
question like, "What AI tools should I
use to develop a video game?" And it
will respond in a way that I'd be likely
to respond. If you're diving into game
development with AI, there's some killer
tools. Google's AI Studio, Leonardo,
Runway, Stable Diffusion, MidJourney,
Luma AI. And well, it's not trained on
the video you're watching right now just
yet. But after this video is live, this
would actually probably be a different
response because it's got essentially
like my brain in it at this point. So,
if you want to check it out and actually
chat with my Deli, my digital clone,
head on over to deli.ai/matwolf
and have a conversation. It's even got a
cool voice mode where you can simulate
having a call with me. Anyway, just
wanted to share that with you really
quick cuz I thought it was cool. Now,
let's get back to chapter 4, refining.
So, I'm going to jump back over to Wind
Surf and just give it a bunch of details
about what I'm seeing. Starting with
stating the obvious, the chaos meter
moves way too fast. You can only last
about 4 seconds when you start the game.
And two, books should start on the
bookshelves. They shouldn't start on the
floor. Kids entering the library are
supposed to be knocking the books off
the bookshelf or picking them up and
running away with them. They shouldn't
already be on the floor when the game
starts. All right, let's try again after
it ran that update and we can see. Okay,
cool. So, the chaos meter isn't moving
yet and all the books are starting on
the bookshelf. I don't like that I can
walk through the bookshelf, so that's
not ideal. And also, I'm not seeing any
kids come in to knock books off the
bookshelf. I also noticed an issue that
if I hold shift, I can move a little bit
faster. And that stamina bar in the top
left moves down really, really fast. But
when I run out of stamina, I can keep on
moving just as fast. It didn't seem to
have any sort of impact whatsoever. So,
I gave it a few notes on what needs to
be fixed based on what I'm seeing. Let's
run it with plan mode and have it map
out a plan for us. So, we've got a new
plan mapped out here. So, let's go ahead
and say yes, auto accept edits, and let
it work through its plan again. From
here, Claude Code spit out a new
version. I was starting to realize that
this was going to need quite a few
rounds of refinement. This version took
about 30 seconds for the NPCs to
actually show up. And for some Oh, wait,
wait. I take that back. We have our
first NPCs at 30 seconds in. The main
character can walk through bookshelves.
The shelves had empty slots without any
books being on the floor. And there were
a bunch of other elements that just
needed some finetuning. So, I gave
Claude Code a new round of instructions,
and it got to work updating the plan and
putting together a new version. This
next one was a bit better, but still
full of holes. The NPCs were constantly
running away to the edges of the map.
Books were still missing on the
bookshelves, and the overall gameplay
logic just wasn't quite dialed in yet.
So, I added another round of
instructions and sent Claude back on its
merry way. And then I did it again. So,
you can see the books are just like
disappearing. And again. They will run
away from me if I try to get close,
which is good. And again. And again. And
again. So, this is actually starting to
be like a fun game now. Let's go chase
this person down. Give me my book. It
ended. My chaos got to 100%. So, it
seems to be working. All right. Now, I
finally got the game to a point where
I'm pretty happy with it. It's actually
fun to play. And it's not too hard, but
also not too easy. And it gets
increasingly more difficult. And this is
the current result of the game. My
little blue square is my librarian. You
can see all the bookshelves. We've
already got two kids knocking books off,
causing havoc. Over here, I could go and
uh put these books on the bookshelf. We
can see the chaos is already starting to
move up, but I can grab a book, put it
on the shelf, knock that chaos back down
by cleaning up after these dang kids. We
have level ups. It will randomly pick
among the three available level ups. I
think we've got five or six total level
ups right now, but you've got things
like increase your maximum stamina,
reduce the chaos gain, how quickly that
chaos meter goes up, increase the
distance you can pick books up from. I'm
going to increase the stamina cuz if I
hold down shift, I can actually sort of
speedrun. But if you look in the top
right, I've got a stamina bar that runs
down. So, I can only run for so long.
And the game is actually legitimately
fun. All of the little kinks and bugs
are worked out. There's just a couple
problems with this still. One, it still
looks ugly. I wasn't shooting for a game
that was just a bunch of rectangles
moving around. And two, there's no sound
effects. It would be nice if there was a
little bit of that like satisfying sound
when you pick up a book and put it on
that shelf. And as you pick up more
books, the sound effects get more rapid
and more satisfying. At this point in
the process, when I have something that
I like and I want to build off of, I
kind of want to back it up. I want to
make sure that I can restore back to
this point. If I start trying to add
graphics and sound effects and do other
stuff and it just totally breaks the
game, I want to be able to jump back to
this sort of save state. And to do that,
I'm going to use GitHub. If you don't
already have a GitHub account and you
want to follow along, make sure you
create a free GitHub account. I'm going
to create a new repository for this
game. I'm going to call this one the
librarian game for now. I'm going to
make it private and I'm just going to
click create repository. That's all I
have to do. So now I have this URL to my
repository,
github.com/misterflow/thelbrarianame.
I will copy this URL to this repository
and I will jump back into Windsurf down
here. Now to do this, I'm actually going
to use Cascade inside of Windsurf
instead of actually having Claude Code
do it. I feel like when I have Cascade
do the backup for me, it actually seems
to do a little bit better job than when
I use Cloud Code. So, I'm going to say,
I created a new private GitHub
repository for this game at
github.com/blah blah blah. Please commit
and push this current version to GitHub.
And it's going to go ahead and just do
the work for me to push it over to
GitHub. And it took about a minute, but
we can see here, perfect. I've
successfully committed and pushed your
library survivors game to GitHub. Here's
what I did. Initialized the Git
repository, added a remote origin,
staged all files, etc. Now, at any
point, if I ever want to, I can actually
come back over to this right side and
say, "Restore my game from this version
on GitHub." If I open up GitHub in my
browser here and just reload this, we
should see all of our files here now.
So, everything is backed up for us on
GitHub, ready to go, and I can restore
from this backup at any time now. Just a
nice little way that if you start going
down the path of building something out
and you just go off in the wrong
direction and it totally gets all messed
up and you go, "Man, I want to restore
from an old save state." Well, this is
what GitHub does for you. It lets you
get back to that old like save state
essentially. So, let's start creating
some graphics for the game. And we'll
start replacing our little rectangles
and background and things like that with
some actual good graphics. I'm going for
more of like a cozy style game, 16bit
graphic kind of thing, similar to like a
Stardew Valley sort of graphics. So, I
started with the floor for our library.
To do this, I jumped into Leonardo and
used Flow for the first handful of
prompts, but I wasn't really getting
what I wanted. I did test out one
version that Flow generated, but got
some ugly tiling when importing it into
the game. So, I went to the regular
image creation section on Leonardo,
clicked to turn on the tile option, and
entered this prompt here, and finally
got something way cooler that fit the
vibe I was looking for. Yeah, this is
this is looking really really good. I
like that background. I think the the
tiling of it is good. The size they
picked of it is good. You can't really
see any seams. Yeah, that's I think
that's our background. Now, we need a
character. We need a librarian character
that's not just like a cube running
around. Next, it was on to our
librarian. I started with this prompt
for the style of the librarian, but was
using Leonardo Phoenix, and it wasn't
quite generating the style I was looking
for that would match that retro 16-bit
vibe. So, I switched over to Lucid
Realism, which is kind of funny because
I was trying to create 16-bit characters
that aren't realistic, but using the
same prompt as before was spitting out
images that were much closer to what I
wanted. Once I settled on a look, I
asked it to make me a second version
with the legs together so that I could
make a basic walking animation. I then
tried out removing the background before
heading back into Claude to implement my
new character changes. After testing a
bit, I saw some issues with the
character size, the image colors, and
how the character looked when standing
still. So, I gave Claude a few new
instructions and realized I would need
to adjust the image colors myself. Now,
it was on to those pesky kids. I first
uploaded the image of our librarian as a
style reference and then asked it to
generate some images of kids who were up
to no good. And for some reason, and I
can't imagine why, all the results were
boys and brunettes. So, I tweaked the
prompt a bit and settled on three
different characters that fit the bill.
Then I repeated the process I did for
the librarian of generating a second
image to simulate walking and removing
the backgrounds. All right. So, I've got
these players dialed in now. They still
have the color issues. I'm going to fix
that in a minute. But you can see we've
got some characters walking around now
that steal the books. We've got multiple
characters. We've got our little
brunette kid, a little red-haired girl,
and then there also should be like a
little blonde character that pops in as
well at some point. And then they just
keep on multiplying as the game goes on,
causing more and more chaos, knocking
more books off the shelf, making the
game harder and harder as you go. I
think we're going to be pretty good on
graphics for this. I'm going to do a a
part two video later on where I actually
rebuild this game in either GDAU or
Unity. And uh we'll really dial in the
graphics when we go for that game. But
this one I wanted to make a basic
JavaScript version. And we've got a
pretty solid game here. So I'm going to
go fix the colors in Photoshop real
quick. Then we'll add some sound effects
and we've got our game. I'm going to do
this real simply. I'm in Photoshop now.
I opened up this character and this
character. We can see that the jacket's
slightly different color on this one.
So, what I'm going to do is I'm just
going to color drop, grab the color of
the jacket here. And I'll jump over to
this one. And we'll make sure the
jacket's the same color on this
character. We'll go ahead and use the
color replacement tool here. And we'll
just paint in the jacket color like so
until we're happy that it looks pretty
much the same. And then I'm going to go
do that for all the characters. And
hopefully we get a much more consistent
color. All right. So, here's where we're
at with the game right now. I actually
created a little background animation
for our loading screen here. Uh,
basically, I just generated an image in
Leonardo, said I wanted it to be like a
Stardew Valley style 16bit animation of
a librarian sitting in the library, and
then I took the image that it made, put
it through VO3 to animate it. And that's
this background that you're seeing
animated here. And I also got rid of the
settings since we didn't have any
settings to change. So, we just have
start game and instructions.
Instructions needs some work here. I
just gave Claude code some instructions
to fix it. And now we have an
instructions page that's actually
readable. So, perfect. When we actually
play the game, there's still some issues
with the characters kind of changing
colors, but you can see our character
walks around. They face in the direction
that they're walking. Our NPCs walk
around. They're little kids. There's a
few different variations of the kids.
We've got our leveling up and the game
is currently working as intended and
pretty much looking as intended as well.
And now that everything's working the
way I want it to, let's add some sound
just to sort of tie it all together and
make it feel like we're actually playing
a game. The gameplay is actually cool.
It's fun. I'm really, really enjoying
it. Every time I sort of demo it or test
it, I find myself like playing for
longer and longer and longer and trying
to beat my last score, which I think is
an indicator that it's a pretty good
game. That's pretty fun. I'm digging it.
But let's get some sound effects in
here. First off, I want some background
music. And to do that, I'm going to jump
over to Suno.ai. I think it'd be cool to
have two songs. one for the sort of main
home screen and then one for when you're
actually playing the game. So, it's not
the same song throughout. So, I'll go to
create. I'm going to turn it on
instrumental. I don't need any lyrics in
this song. And I'm going to do lowfi
cozy retro video game music. Calming
soothing. I just want it to be like
relaxing, comfy music. So, let's see
what it gives us for that. Here's the
first version.
Let's go ahead and download it. Toss it
into our assets here. Copy the path. Set
this song as the background music for
the opening menu screen. Loop the song.
And it finishes playing. All right. So,
it should set that as our opening
background song. And while it's
generating that, let's go back to Sunno
and generate another one. I'm going to
use the same prompt again.
[Music]
I'll pull this other song into Wind Surf
into my assets folder as well. Copy the
path, paste that in there, and let it
set that as the background to the actual
game play. And then I also want some
sound effects. So for the sound effects,
we're going to go to 11 Labs, and they
actually have a sound effects generator
over here. Let's see what happens if I
just do like menu select. Kind of like
this one. this sample three here. Let's
download that. Pull this menu select
sound into our assets. And then I'll
start typing up my prompt while it's
still working on our background music
here. So I'll copy the path here and say
on the menu screen, use this audio when
a new menu item is selected. And now I
finally got a game that I'm actually
pretty happy with. We've got our main
menu with our background music,
our instructions. Let's go ahead and
start a game. The game volume was a
touch loud, but as you can hear with
this clean recording, we added all of
our music. A really satisfying thud when
you drop a book off, kids giggling when
they're being little jerks, and I even
added a sound effect for when you run
out of stamina. You'll also notice from
this gameplay recording that I was able
to fix the graphics using Photoshop and
made some additional minor tweaks to the
pace of the gameplay. But overall, this
game is really fun and kind of
addictive. I was able to do all of this
in a day, and I'm going to continue
refining and improving over the next
couple of weeks. I'm thinking part two
of this series will be moving the game
over to Unity or GDAU, where I can
really take the game to the next level.
But in the meantime, here's a link to
both the game and the GitHub, which will
also be linked up in the description so
you can try it out or even take it and
make your own version. If you do make
your own version, please link me up over
on X so I can try it out. Thank you so
much for nerding out with me. I hope you
enjoyed this video and learned something
from it. I'm super excited to keep
working on this game and hopefully I'll
see you in part two. Bye-bye.
[Music]
Thank you so much for nerding out with
me today. If you like videos like this,
make sure to give it a thumbs up and
subscribe to this channel. I'll make
sure more videos like this show up in
your YouTube feed. And if you haven't
already, check out futuretools.io where
I share all the coolest AI tools and all
the latest AI news and there's an
awesome free newsletter. Thanks again.
Really appreciate you. See you in the
next one.